Hello, everyone, and welcome to this just in.
I'm here with Bill.
Ow, I'm Bill.
And Scarlett, that's...
Hi.
Scarlett's looking at me.
He's like, why do you always introduce Bill first?
Every time, every single time.
Because he's on my right.
You know, I go...
I'm opposite you.
You're looking at me right now.
I should be the priority.
Whatever.
He likes me better.
I don't think so.
All right, all right.
So today, we are joined with these two lovely people who are always fighting that are going
to help me introduce next week's lessons.
Yay.
Yeah.
All right.
So on Monday, we have a lesson all about going to the deli.
Mmm, yeah.
I like going to the deli.
Do you like pickles?
I love pickles.
God, why do people love pickles?
Because they taste...
What's wrong with you?
They taste great.
I like...
They look awful.
Yeah.
They don't look that bad.
They're nasty water.
Oh, I love the brine.
Sometimes I drink the brine.
Ew.
I did when I was a kid.
I still would.
But...
What about...
It's frowned upon by most people.
Olives.
I love olives.
I just love really salty things.
I hate olives.
Oh, I hate olives too.
What's wrong with you people?
They just rank things.
That's fine.
More for me.
Well, that's basically what you get at the deli.
You get pickles, olives.
You can get cheeses.
You get meats.
Yeah, meats.
And meats.
Most importantly, what's your favorite cured meat?
I would say...
I usually go for smoked turkey.
Smoked turkey.
I like turkey a lot.
I like turkey ham.
And I like turkey more than ham.
You know, if I wasn't counting calories, I'd eat pastrami and I like salami all the time.
Because that's bad for your heart.
It is?
Oh, yeah.
Why?
Because it's full of fat and cholesterol.
But it's good.
I know.
It's because of the fat and cholesterol that it's good.
What about you, Scarlett?
Probably the ham.
I really like ham.
Yeah.
Smoked ham.
But I'll eat anything from the deli, apart from pickles and olives.
What about cheese?
Are you guys a big fan of cheese?
Yeah.
Yeah, I could eat cheese all day.
What's your favorite cheese?
I do like a sharp cheddar.
Do you now?
I do.
I mean...
A very sharp cheddar.
So what do you mean by sharp cheddar?
Yeah.
Like a strong?
Extra sharp cheddar.
So that means it has a strong taste.
Yeah, it's real strong, pungent.
Cool.
What are we going to be looking at on Monday?
Oh, and apart from that, I also must say that I don't like coleslaw.
What?
Tell them about coleslaw.
Coleslaw?
Can we talk about actual sandwiches that you guys like?
I like grilled cheese sandwich.
Yeah, you can't really get a grilled cheese at the deli, though, I think.
No.
I do like pastrami and pepperoni, and I am now a big fan of Polish sausage.
Ah.
Kielbasa.
Yeah.
I really like a Reuben.
Reubens?
Yeah.
I know a Reuben.
I don't like them, though.
A Reuben sandwich?
You don't like them?
A Reuben is, correct me if I'm wrong, listeners, it's a rye bread with pastrami and Swiss cheese
and coleslaw, actually.
You put coleslaw in it.
And that's a sandwich.
Yeah.
I don't know how I feel about coleslaw in a sandwich.
Ooh, it's so delicious.
Think about it.
No.
We're no longer friends.
Weren't we friends, anyway?
We were best friends, weren't we?
Oh, yeah.
News to me.
Okay.
That's on Monday.
On Tuesday, we're going to talk about Director's Cut.
That's our movie show.
And we're going to take a look at the Academy Award-winning movie, The Hurt Locker.
Have you seen this movie yet?
Nope.
No?
Who's in it?
No one famous, I think, but it's directed by Catherine Bigelow, who was the first woman
ever to win an Academy Award.
Oh, on International Women's Day, wasn't it?
No, I think it was like a day before.
Yeah.
But, yeah, it's a good one.
And so we're going to talk about that film.
It's a really good film.
On Wednesday, we are taking a look at health food, healthy food.
Okay.
After the deli.
Now we're going to take a look at it.
Fat it up a little bit, and then some...
So really boring foods that just don't taste good.
Yeah.
It's actually some health food I like.
It's hard to find healthy food that actually tastes as good as...
It fills you up.
Yeah.
If you have a craving, you don't go for healthy food.
What do you guys think of as quintessential healthy food?
Well, like, it's a lot of veggies.
Fruit.
And non-fried things.
Like, fried things are so delicious.
They are.
So non-fried things.
And non-salty things, usually.
Non-salty.
Non-sweet things.
Non-sweet.
See, it takes away everything that's good about food.
Exactly.
But it's been too...
It's been commoditized, I think, health food.
How?
There's a certain stigma attached to health food, when really, to eat healthy just means
that you shouldn't eat things that are, like, made in a factory.
You know what I mean?
True.
Like, if you just ate, like, natural foods.
And also...
Even if you have a big hunk of steak, like...
Exactly.
That's okay.
I mean, it's...
I think the worst thing for you is to eat all these processed foods.
Yeah.
And I think also, even if you do cook fatty foods, but it's home-cooked meals, I think
it's a lot healthier than fast food.
Definitely.
It's better for the environment as well.
Microwave things.
Yeah.
It was actually one of the things that I was very surprised on my recent trip to the U.S.,
back to the U.S., is how people's diets and how fast food is just this huge thing.
Oh, yeah.
You know?
Like, people don't really eat at home, or they don't have a proper lunch.
Sure.
I mean, it speaks to a bigger problem, I think, of just people...
Everyone's always on the go.
Always on the go in instant gratification, and just the pace of life is too fast.
It's crazy, though.
It is crazy to think that you can get a burger for 99 cents, but a head of lettuce costs like
$1.50.
Yeah.
It's unfair.
It really is.
Did you go to In-N-Out when you were in the U.S.?
Yeah.
What's In-N-Out?
It's this hamburger place.
All they serve is like...
That's like...
Actually, it's a family business in California, and they use all-natural ingredients, like
their milkshakes don't, or just like cream, ice, and like, you know.
Yeah.
You can taste the difference in the burgers and, you know, like even the fries, for example.
They're actually real potatoes.
Yeah.
You can see them do the potatoes.
Well, anyways...
I love...
I had a high-fridged job there once.
And you didn't get it?
They didn't call me back.
Why?
They're actually...
They're really...
Selective?
They're really selective.
They don't just let anyone in.
I had a really hard time at some funny job.
I actually...
I was done with college.
Or no, I was halfway through college, and I was like applying to be like a dishwasher.
I'm like working here.
Yeah.
Nobody wanted me.
Oh, man.
I know.
Well, I think now with your new acquired skills and experience, you can definitely get a job
there.
Don't feel too rejected.
Thanks, Marco.
All right.
That's on Wednesday.
On Friday, we are doing something good for the community.
We're volunteering.
Wow, really?
Really volunteering?
We're just having a lesson about...
About...
We're having a lesson about volunteering.
But actually, it is...
We'll inspire some of our listeners to go out and volunteer.
Yeah.
Have you ever done any volunteer work?
Sure.
I've done lots of volunteer work.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Like what?
I...
I volunteered for the Northwest AIDS Foundation for a few months.
What'd you do?
I went to...
It was actually kind of a cool volunteer gig because I got to go see like plays and
musicals and stuff.
And then just during the intermission, I would like solicit donations to the organizations.
But then, you know, during when it was actually going on, I could sit and watch.
That's cool.
Yeah.
How about you, Scarlett?
Have you done any volunteer work?
I'm trying to think.
This probably sounds quite bad.
I actually saw that your brother is doing some awesome things on the internet.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, he's raising funds, right?
Yeah, he's running the London Marathon to raise money for spinal research.
That's cool.
Yeah, it's not too bad.
So that's kind of like volunteering.
He's volunteering to run for her cause.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's why my brother is volunteering.
Yeah, shut up.
I didn't think we'd home in on that detail.
What about you, Marco?
Have you done some volunteer work?
I have done community service.
A court order?
No, I wasn't forced to do it, but I've done a couple of things like that.
I don't know.
I was thinking of actually going to some place that is like poor and maybe teaching
English for a while or something like that.
That's good.
Cool.
Yeah, I mean, I have a friend who joined the Peace Corps.
That's intense.
That's hardcore.
Two years in an African small village.
For two years non-stop.
Can you imagine that?
That is hardcore.
Yeah.
I mean, like you think about volunteer work is like two or three months maybe at most
for two years.
Yeah, I think that's good because then you really have a sense of what the community
needs rather than just deciding what they need, you know?
Actually I was thinking I once I remember I wanted to be a volunteer firefighter.
That would have been cool.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know.
What do you do as a volunteer firefighter though?
You're a firefighter for free.
Oh, you should do that.
Yeah, I know.
You should be the office's volunteer firefighter or a safety monitor and you could remind us
about different safety things.
Yeah, like to not leave your backpack near the exit area.
Yeah, you could give out little tickets and stuff if people have violated the rules.
That's a good idea.
Maybe you could generate some extra income.
Oh, no, this is volunteers.
This is volunteers.
You don't get money for this.
Okay.
All right, so those are our lessons coming up next week.
They're really interesting and you're definitely going to learn a lot from them.
And do you guys have any news, any interesting questions that may have come up from our users?
I know some people have been having some problems downloading the lessons.
Not like problems, but they can't really figure out because you click on it and it takes you
to a media player, like a built-in web browser, quick time player.
Right.
So there's a few different ways you can download.
So the first way, the simplest way is if you just right click on the episode file.
So there'll be the lesson file, we'll say the lesson.mp3 or whatever.
I don't have a computer in front of me right now, unfortunately, but you can just right
click on it if you have a PC and then just save it directly to your hard drive.
So you say right click and then save.
Save this link as.
Yeah.
And then the other way is setting up iTunes to work with your RSS feed, which is a little
bit more complicated, but it's not very difficult.
You just need to go to your archive, I believe in English pod.
And then from there you right click on your RSS feed.
You copy it and then paste it into iTunes or whatever podcasting application you might
have.
Okay.
So, um, yeah, if you guys have any doubts or any other questions or you need help, you
can always send an email to support, right?
Yeah.
What's the email address?
Support at Praxislanguage.com.
All right.
So that's all the time we have for today.
We'll see you guys next time and take care.
Bye.
EnglishPod.com.